A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.29 (A2003) FA490
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2003.107: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2003; AC.2003.107; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 standard record storage boxes, R3613-R3615 and R3619-R3623.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - SCHOLARS (URRY, SERENA), 1996-1999 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (URSACHI, MIHAI), 1995-2002 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (VAIDERE, INESE), 1996-1999 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (VAN DER RYN SIM), 1996-1997 (Box R3623A)
    - SCHOLARS (VARI-SZILAGYI, IBOLYA), 1996-1999 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (VASALY, ANN CAROL), 1996-1997 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (VERSCHUEREN, JEF), 1995-1998 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (VINING, JOSEPH), 1996-1997 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (WANG, XIAOMING), 1996-1997 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (WEBB, CHARLES H.), 1993-1997 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (WESTOFF, CHARLES F.), 1997-1998 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (WIGGINS, DAVID), 1996-1998 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (WIMSATT, WILLIAM C.), 1995-1997 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (WOODS, MICHAEL), 1995-1997 (Box R3623)
- AC.2003.112: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2003; AC.2003.112; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3616-R3618.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.112.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 97016 #192; RF 98017 #193 - (UNDERSTANDING CULTURES THROUGH MUSEUMS) - "KEYWORD" CONFERENCES, 1997-2003 (Box R3616)
    - RF 98013 #186 - (POLICY RESEARCH AND DIALOGUE) - SYMPOSIUM, "POPULATION AND OUR GLOBAL FUTURE", 1998-1999 (Box R3616)
    - RF 98014 #23 - INTERNATIONAL UNION FOR THE SCIENTIFIC STUDY OF POPULATION (BELGIUM) - NAIROBI SEMINARS ON REPRODUCTIVE CHANGE IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1997-2003 (Box R3616)
    - RF 98016 - NAUTILUS OF AMERICA - NORTHEAST ASIA PEACE AND SECUITY NETWORK, 1993-2001 (Box R3616)
    - RF 98017 #194 - GUADALUPE CULTURAL ARTS CENTER - EXHIBITION, "THE ROLE OF PAPER: AFFIRMATION AND IDENTITY", 1997-2000 (Box R3616)
    - RF 98017 #195 - ASIA SOCIETY - EXHIBITION, "INSIDE OUT: NEW CHINESE ART", 1997-2002 (Box R3616)
    - RF 98017 #196 - YERBA BUENA GARDENS CULTURAL CENTER - FESTIVAL, "A MEXICAN PRESENCE', 1997-1999 (Box R3616)
    - RF 98017 #198 - ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION, " CONTEMPORARY ART FROM CUBA", 1996-1999 (Box R3616)
    - RF 98017 #199 - AMERICAN ACADEMY OF ARTS AND SCIENCES - DAEDALUS ISSUE ON MUSEUMS, 1997-2000 (Box R3616)
    - RF 98017 #200 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - EXHIBITION, "DEVI: THE GREAT GODDESS", 1997-2000 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #201 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND - EXHIBITION, "DAVID C. DRISKELL COLLECTION", 1997-2000 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #202 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - "SMITHSONIAN WITHOUT WALLS PROJECT", 1995-2002 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #204 - SOUTHEASTERN CENTER FOR CONTEMPORARY ART - EXHIBITION, "INIGO MANGLANO-OVALLE: THE GARDEN OF DELIGHTS", 1998-2002 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #205 - BROOKLYN MUSEUM OF ART - EXHIBITION, "THE QAJAR EPOCH", 1998-1999 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #206 - PUEBLO OF POJOAQUE - "NAH-POEH-ME" EXHIBITION, 1997-1999 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #207 - WALKER ART CENTER - "UNFINISHED HISTORY" EXHIBITION, 1998-1999 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #208 - EXIT ART/THE FIRST WORLD - CONTEMPORARY ART PROGRAM, "FUTURAMA", 1998-2002 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #209 - CONTEMPORARY ART FOR SAN ANTONIO - "LATINA POSTCOLONIAL PHOTOBUREAU" RESIDENCY AND INSTALLATION PROJECT, 1998-1999 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #210 - MEXICAN FINE ARTS CENTER MUSEUM - "CALENDARIO", AN EXHIBITION, 1998-2002 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #212 - MEXICAN MUSEUM - "PRESCIOUS COMFORTS", EXHIBITION OF WORK OF PATSSI VALDEZ, 1998-2000 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #213 - BIRMINGHAM MUSEUM OF ART - EXHIBITION, "CHOKWE! ART AND INITIATION AMONG CHOKWE AND RELATED PEOPLES", 1998-2002 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98017 #214 - OHIO HISTORICAL SOCIETY - "WHEN THE SPIRIT MOVES?", 1998-1999 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98019 #6 - ORGANIZE TRAINING CENTER - GROUP DISCUSSIONS WITH LABOR LEADERS IN SAN FRANCISCO, 1998-1999 (Box R3617)
    - RF 98019 #7 - METROPOLITAN AREA RESEARCH CORPORATION - SOCIOECONOMIC DISPARITY IN METROPOLITAN AREAS, 1998-2001 (Box R3617)
    - RF 97018 #23; RF 98020 #24 - UNITED WAY OF THE BAY AREA - LABOR MARKET STUDY OF THE HOSPITALITY INDUSTRY, 1998-2001 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98019 #12 - GAMALIEL FOUNDATION - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1998 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98019 #14 - JOBS WITH JUSTICE EDUCATION FUND - ANNUAL CONFERENCE, 1999-2002 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98019 #8 - LOS ANGELES ALLIANCE FOR A NEW ECONOMY - TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE TO GRASSROOTS ADVOCACY GROUPS, 1998-1999 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98020 #32 - WORKING PARTNERSHIPS USA - MEETING ON LABOR MARKET INTERMEDIARIES, 1998-2001 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98020 #34 - NATIONAL BUREAU Of ECONOMIC RESEARCH, INC. - SURVEY OF U.S. WORKERS AND FORMS OF SHARED COMPENSATION/OWNERSHIP, 1999-2001 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98023 #10 - SOCIETY FOR INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT (ITALY) - ROUNDTABLE AND PUBLICATION ON GLOBALIZATION AND PUBLIC HEALTH, 1998-2000 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98023 #12 - (INITIATIVES FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH) - MEETING ON STRENGTHENING DISEASE SURVEILLANCE IN MEKONG BASIN, 1999 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98023 #20 - (INITIATIVES FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH) - MEETING ON "CURRENT ACTIVITIES AND FUTURE DIRECTIONS FOR HEALTH EQUITY", 1999 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98023 #21 - (INITIATIVES FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH) - MEETING ON TOBACCO CONTROL IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1999 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98023 #28 - CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - WORKSHOP ON GLOBAL HEALTH EQUITY INDICATORS, 1999-2002 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98023 #7 - CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - "SOCIAL INEQUALITIES AND HEALTH IN AN INTERMEDIATE DEVELOPMENT NATION: CHILE 1980-1996", 1998-2000 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98023 #8 - LONDON SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND TROPICAL MEDICINE (ENGLAND) - FORUM ON "POVERTY, INEQUALITY AND HEALTH", 1998-1999 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98025 #10 - LABOR COMMUNITY STRATEGY CENTER - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1996-1999 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98025 #13 - COMMUNITY PARTNERS - PUBLIC SUPPORT FOR INCLUSIVE APPROACHES TO EDUCATIONAL OPPORTUNITY, 1998-2003 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98025 #14 - FAITH AND POLITICS INSTITUTE - CONGRESSIONAL CONVERSATIONS ON RACE, 1995-1999 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98025 #4 - NATIONAL CIVIC LEAGUE OF COLORADO - RACE AWARD PROJECT, 1998-2000 (Box R3618)
    - RF 98025 #5 - CHILDREN NOW - CHILDREN AND THE MEDIA PROGRAM'S RACE, CLASS AND MEDIA FOCUS, 1998-1999 (Box R3618)
- AC.2003.119: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2002; AC.2003.119; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3624.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.119.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 98027 #342 - AMERICAN REPERTORY THEATRE - PLAY ON NOTION OF IMAGE, "VALPARAISO", 1998-2000 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #343 - ASIA SOCIETY - MUSIC THEATER WORK, "FORGIVENESS", 1998-2000 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #344 - BATES DANCE FESTIVAL - BALLET, "ROME AND JEWELS: SHAKESPEARE MEETS HIP HOP", 1998-2000 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #346 - BRAVA FOR WOMEN IN THE ARTS - "THE CALLE VEINTICUATRO PROJECT: RADIO SAN FRANCISCO", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #348 - CHILDREN'S THEATER COMPANY AND SCHOOL - MULTl MEDIA WORK ON LIFE OF GALLILEO, 1998-2000 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #349 - CORNERSTONE THEATER COMPANY - MULTl-LINGUAL MUSICAL THEATER PIECE, "THE BH BRIDGE PROJECT", 1998-2000 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #351 - DANSPACE PROJECT - NEW WORKS THROUGH CULTURAL EXCHANGES OF US AND ARGENTINE ARTISTS, 1998-1999 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #353 - BYRD DANCE FOUNDATION - "THE MELDING OF TRADITIONS: FOSTERING A NEW AMERICAN BALLET REPERTOIRE", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #354 - DUKE UNIVERSITY - DANCE OPERA, "LUYALA", 1998-2000 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #355 - FIJI THEATER CO. - WORK EXPLORING RELATIONS BETWEEN KOREA AND U.S., 1998-2000 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #356 - FOUNDATION FOR INDEPENDENT ARTISTS - DANCE THEATER WORK, "BIBLE STORIES", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #357 - GAMELAN SEKAR JAYA - MUSIC WORKS INTEGRATING GAMELAN AND OTHER ENSEMBLES, 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #358 - GEORGE COATES PERFORMANCE WORKS - MULTIMEDIA WORK, "THE BLIND MESSENGER", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #359 - HALLWALLS - MUSICAL, "THE SHADOW CATCHERS", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #360 - HELENA PRESENTS - MULTI-COMMUNITY PROJECT ON MUSICAL LEGACY OF METIS PEOPLE, 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #361 - HOUSE FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - MULTIMEDIA THEATER WORK, "PLANETARY MOVES", 1996-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #362 - INTA - MOBILE PERFORMANCE WORK, "THE CARAVAN PROJECT: WHEN NIGHTS WERE DARK", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #365 - LERMAN DANCE EXCHANGE - DANCE COLLABORATION, "HALLELUJAH", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #366 - JENKINS DANCE STUDIO - DANCE-THEATER WORK, "TIME AFTER", 1998-1999 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #367 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - THEATRICAL WORK, "AUTOMATIC EARTH", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #368 - OTHER MINDS - VISUAL PERCUSSION WORK, "SIGHT OF HAND", 1998-2001 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #369 - FIELD (THE) - MULTIMEDIA WORK, "DE FLOR", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #370 - PORTLAND INSTITUTE FOR CONTEMPORARY ART - MULTIMEDIA PERFORMANCE WORK, "THE INCREDIBLE DISAPPEARING WOMAN", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #371 - REAL ART WAYS - MULTIMEDIA WORK, "THESE HANDS", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #372 - REICH MUSIC FOUNDATION - VIDEO OPERA, "THREE TALES", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #373 - RIDGE STREET THEATRE - MULTIMEDIA WORK BASED ON WORK OF HENRY DARGER, 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #374 - SALVAGE VANGUARD THEATER - OPERA, "AJLINNA ID-DIBAYIH IN NIGHT VISION", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #375 - SCHOOL OF HARD KNOCKS - DANCE WORK, "FOOTPRINTS OF WAR", 1998-2002 (Box R3624)
    - RF 98027 #376 - SOLOMONS COMPANY/DANCE - "CREDO," A DANCE WORK, 1998-2000 (Box R3624)
- AC.2003.121: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2003; AC.2003.121; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3625-R3628.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.121.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 98027 #377 - WOOSTER GROUP - THEATRICAL COLLABORATION, "NORTH ATLANTIC", 1998-2000 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98027 #378 - YALE UNIVERSITY - "GEOGRAPHY, PART 2: ASIA", 1998-2000 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98029 #32 - CORPORATION FOR SUPPORTIVE HOUSING - PLACE-BASED EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR FAMILIES; NEXT STEP: JOBS, 1998-2002 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98029 #33 - SAN FRANCISCO FOUNDATION COMMUNITY INITIATIVE FUNDS - IMPROVE EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITIES FOR BAYVIEW HUNTER'S POINT NEIGHBORHOOD, 1997-1999 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98029 #36 - CENTER FOR LAW AND SOCIAL POLICY - MEETING ON PUBLIC JOBS PROGRAMS; POLICY ANALYSIS AND TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE, 1999-2003 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98031 #47 - ALBUQUERQUE PUBLIC SCHOOLS - ACADEMIC EQUITY AUDIT, 1998-2002 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98031 #54 - EDUCATION COMMISSION OF THE STATES - MEETING ON TEACHER QUALITY, 1999-2000 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98031 #55 - INSTITUTE FOR RESEARCH AND REFORM IN EDUCATION - EVALUATION PLAN FOR FLINT COMMUNITY SCHOOLS' THEORY OF CHANGE, 1999 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98032 #21 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - NATIONAL COMMUNITY BUILDING NETWORK, 1993-2000 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98032 #21 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - NATIONAL COMMUNITY BUILDING NETWORK - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2000 (Box R3625)
    - RF 98032 #27 - CENTER FOR JUVENILE AND CRIMINAL JUSTICE - DECLINING PRISONS, 1996-2000 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98032 #27 - CENTER FOR JUVENILE AND CRIMINAL JUSTICE - DECLINING PRISONS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-2000 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #37 - FAMILY RESOURCE COALITION OF AMERICA - PARENT EDUCATION CURRICULUM, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98032 #20 - CLEVELAND COMMUNITY BUILDING INITIATIVE - COMMUNICATION AND DATA COLLECTION, 1998 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98032 #29 - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT SOCIETY OF AMERICA - CONFERENCE ON COMMUNITY BUILDING, 1999-2003 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #38 - JUSTICE MATTERS, INC. - NON-PROFIT PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT LEADERSHIP TRAINING, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #39 - BASOMBRIO, ISABELA - ART-MAKING; DOCUMENTATION AND INVESTIGATION OF OPPORTUNITIES FOR EXHIBITION OF ARTWORK, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #40 - COMMUNITY OF HOPE, INC. - COMMUNITY BUILDING PROGRAM IN THE INNER-CITY OF WASHINGTON, DC, 1998-1999 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #41 - STRATEGIC CONCEPTS IN ORGANIZING AND POLICY EDUCATION - COMMUNITY LEADERSHIP AND WELFARE RECIPIENTS, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #42 - EAST HARLEM SCHOOL AT EXODUS HOUSE - PILOT EDUCATIONAL EXCHANGE PROJECT, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #43 - INSIGHT ARTS - "THE FEAR OF FREEDOM" WORKSHOP, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #44 - NATIONAL COALITION TO ABOLISH THE DEATH PENALTY - MEDIA CAMPAIGN ON JUVENILE DEATH PENALTY, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #46 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND (BALTIMORE) - BUILD CAPACITY OF RESIDENTS IN LOW-INCOME AND MINORITY COMMUNITIES WITH TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #48 - LAWYERS' COMMITTEE FOR CIVIL RIGHTS OF THE SAN FRANCISCO BAY AREA - TEACHING YOUTH ABOUT CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS AND POLICE REFORM, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #49 - TIDES CENTER - STUDENTS FOR RESPONSIBLE BUSINESS' PHILANTHROPY NETWORKS, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #53 - WESTERN STATES CENTER - EDUCATION ON ISSUES OF IMMIGRATION, ENVIRONMENT AND SOCIAL JUSTICE, 1996-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #54 - PUBLIC ALLIES: THE NATIONAL CENTER FOR CAREERS IN PUBLIC LIFE - LEADERSHIP IN COMMUNITIES POLL; CONFERENCE, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #55 - SISTERS OF MERCY OF THE AMERICAS, AUBURN REGIONAL COMMUNITY - HELP NEW IMMIGRANTS ADJUST TO U.S. LIFE; PRODUCE HANDBOOK ON LESSONS LEARNED, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #56 - TIMONER, RACHEL D. - MULTl-ISSUE, MULTl-CONTITUENCY MOVEMENT, 1998-2002 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #57 - BAUER, HILARIA R. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #58 - BENJAMIN, REGINA M. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #59 - COUPOUNAS, DEMETRIOS - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3626)
    - RF 98037 #60 - DE NOBRIGA, KATHIE E. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #61 - FORMAN, MARK L. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #62 - GARCETTI, ERIC M. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #63 - GROSS, DANIEL N. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #64 - HOROWITZ, SARA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #65 - HORWITZ, CLAUDIA B. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #66 - HOWARD, TIMOTHEA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #67 - HOYOS, LISA A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #68 - JOHNSON, MARTIN P. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #69 - KERR, OTHO, E. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #70 - KHOKHA, SASHA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #71 - MEADOFF, LAURIE E. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #72 - PAGES, ERIK R. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2002 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #73 - PATRICK, STEPHEN - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #74 - PINEDA, CARLOS E. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #75 - PINKETT, PRESTON D. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #76 - SCOTT, JASON A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #77 - SOLOMON, MARC - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #78 - URQUILLA, MARIAN - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #79 - WASHINAWATOK, INGRID E. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98037 #80 - WASOW, OMAR T. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98046 - OVERSEAS DEVELOPMENT COUNCIL - PROGRAMATIC TRANSITION, 1998-2000 (Box R3627)
    - RF 98048 #7 - NATIONAL MUSEUMS OF KENYA - NATIONAL WORKSHOP ON PROTECTION OF PLANT GENETIC RESOURCES, 1999-2002 (Box R3628)
    - RF 98049 #35 - DOCTORS WITHOUT BORDERS - MEETING ON ACCESS TO DRUG TREATMENTS FOR DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1999-2000 (Box R3628)
    - RF 98059 - CHILDREN'S DEFENSE FUND - BLACK COMMUNITY CRUSADE FOR CHILDREN, 1991-2000 (Box R3628)
    - RF 98059 - CHILDREN'S DEFENSE FUND - BLACK COMMUNITY CRUSADE FOR CHILDREN - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2000 (Box R3628)
- AC.2003.123: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2002; AC.2003.123; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3629-R3631.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.123.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 98060 - COMMUNITY-BUILDING POLICY CENTER, 1997-1998 (Box R3629)
    - RF 99001 #709 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE VARIETAL DEVELOPMENT, 1998-2002 (Box R3629)
    - RF 99001 #718 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - LEAF FOLDER RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1996-1999 (Box R3629)
    - RF 99001 #720 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - WORKSHOP, "BIOINFORMATICS AND APPLICATIONS OF CANDIDATE GENES", 1999 (Box R3629)
    - RF 99001 #723 - SOUTH CHINA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - VECTOR SYSTEM FOR MAP-BASED CLONING OF RICE GENES, 1996-1999 (Box R3629)
    - RF 99001 #725 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - TRANSGENIC RICE LINES OF INDICA CULTIVARS, 1994-2002 (Box R3629)
    - RF 99001 #736 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - MOLECULAR MAPPING OF RICE USING MICRO-SATELLITE-DNA MARKERS, 1999-2002 (Box R3630)
    - RF 99001 #743 - FOUNDATION FOR RESEARCH IN APPLIED BIOLOGY (FIBA) (ARGENTINA) - BIOCHEMICAL AND MOLECULAR APPROACH TO INCREASE RICE PRODUCTION, 1994-2001 (Box R3630)
    - RF 99001 #750 - DONALD DANFORTH PLANT SCIENCE CENTER - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR DEVELOPING-COUNTRY SCIENTISTS, 1992-2002 (Box R3630)
    - RF 99006 #150 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - MAIN MAIZE DISEASES, 1995-1999 (Box R3630)
    - RF 99006 #156 - AFRICAN CROP SCIENCE SOCIETY (SOUTH AFRICA) - 1999 CONGRESS AND PUBLICATION OF THE JOURNAL, 1998-2000 (Box R3630)
    - RF 99006 #171 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - TECHNOLOGY AND AFRICAN SOIL FERTILITY, 1996-2002 (Box R3630)
    - RF 99006 #175 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - DEVELOPMENT OF ITS PROGRAMS, 1998-2001 (Box R3630)
    - RF 99009 #208 - POPULATION ACTION INTERNATIONAL - PUBLICATION PROGRAM AND MEDIA ACTIVITIES, 1996-2000 (Box R3630)
    - RF 99009 #208 - POPULATION ACTION INTERNATIONAL - PUBLICATION PROGRAM AND MEDIA ACTIVITIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-2000 (Box R3630)
    - RF 99015 #37 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE AND BOOK CHAPTER ON INTERNATIONAL IMMIGRATION, 1999-2001 (Box R3631)
    - RF 99009 #217 - WORLD POPULATION FOUNDATION (NETHERLANDS) - EUROPEAN DONOR ASSISTANCE FOR POPULATION IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1993-2001 (Box R3631)
    - RF 99016 #23 - FREMONT PUBLIC ASSOCIATION - COMMUNITY JOBS PROGRAM IN WASHINGTON STATE, 1997-2000 (Box R3631)